nsearch.com 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Project Nsearch

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked for your name or email address.  You may however visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways.

To personalize your experience (your information allows us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website (we constantly get new ideas from our users)

To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions and notify contest winners

Your information, whether public or private will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or given for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to this website or an order you make.  We also send out periodic website news, updates and information.

Note at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

The company that administers this site, Ning, uses a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.  Financial information is never store on our servers but only with the bank that processes the payments.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, we use basic cookies to enhance your experience on the website.  None of it is stored or tracked in any way.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information for any reason.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.  These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies.  We therefore have no responsibility of these linked sites.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page.

This policy was last modified 4/19/11
